A Guide to the Foundation for Child Development records FA019
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Programs, 1911, 1946-1996, bulk 1960-1996; bulk; 4
  - Child Trends, Inc., 1978-1984, 1987-1992; 2
    - Papers - 'U.S. Children and Their Families: Current Conditions and Recent Trends', 1981-1984 (Reel 47, Frame 88)
    - Papers - 'Planning', 1977-1980 (Reel 47, Frame 130)
    - Papers - 'Proposals to the Foundation for Child Development', 1979, 1982-1984, 1989-1990 (Reel 47, Frame 310)
  - Ecology of Human Development Program, 1973-1982, 1984, 1989-1990; 3
    This separate allocation engaged a number of institutions to study "the ecological factors promoting or hindering healthy development to justify the recommendation of particular child-care policies and programs." A major consultant in this program was Dr. Urie Bronfenbrenner of Cornell University, who designed a research program to gather epidemiologic and demographic data to reveal the effect of ecological and environmental factors upon developmental health. The first policy study group met on October 3, 1972, to discuss the parameters of this research project; an Advisory Committee next met on March 14, 1973, to propose the adoption of Dr. Bronfenbrenner's approach and outline objectives and criteria for research proposals. Adopting a multi-institutional approach, the Advisory Committee reviewed proposals for endeavors of one to three years.
    The institutions selected for participation are individually documented in this subseries.
    - Series 4.3 - Grant Programs - Ecology of Human Development Program, 1973-1982, 1984, 1989-1990 (Reel 47, Frame 472)
    - Case Western Reserve University, 1975-1974 (Reel 47, Frame 473)
    - Cornell University - Ecology of Human Development - Urie Bronfenbrenner, 1973-1975, 1977-1978, 1981-1982 (Reel 47, Frame 558)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants, 1973-1982 (Reel 47, Frame 771)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - William Alvarez, 1980-1981 (Reel 47, Frame 772)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Jay Belsky, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 785)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Karen Blum, 1979 (Reel 47, Frame 794)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Margaret Campbell, 1978-1979 (Reel 47, Frame 805)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Avshalom Caspi, n.d. (Reel 47, Frame 853)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Rebekah L. Dorman, 1980 (Reel 47, Frame 866)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Gay Eastman, 1980 (Reel 47, Frame 878)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Linda Gerson, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 889)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Susan J. Johnson, 1980-1982 (Reel 47, Frame 903)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Janet Kalinowski, 1980 (Reel 47, Frame 915)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Amy Koel, 1977-1978 (Reel 47, Frame 917)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Mary Larner, n.d. (Reel 47, Frame 982)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - David Riley, 1982 (Reel 47, Frame 984)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Steve Small, 1980 (Reel 47, Frame 993)
    - Cornell University - Fellowship Applicants - Karen Weinberg, 1973 (Reel 47, Frame 1023)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part I, 1973-1979 (Reel 48, Frame 1)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part I - Eduardo Almeida, 1974-1976 (Reel 48, Frame 2)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part I - Jane Brassard, 1976-1977 (Reel 48, Frame 132)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part I - Lyn Chambers, 1976-1977 (Reel 48, Frame 194)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part II, 1973-1978 (Reel 48, Frame 211)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part II - Moncrieff Cochran, 1974-1976 (Reel 48, Frame 212)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part III, 1973-1978 (Reel 48, Frame 515)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part III - Moncrieff Cochran, 1977-1978 (Reel 48, Frame 516)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV, 1973-1978 (Reel 48, Frame 719)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV - Barbara Koslowski and Lyn Chambers, 1974-1977 (Reel 48, Frame 720)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV - Maureen A. Mahoney, 1974 (Reel 48, Frame 832)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV - Janice Molnar, 1978-1980 (Reel 48, Frame 898)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV - Mary Moran, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 908)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV - David L. Olds, 1974-1977 (Reel 48, Frame 916)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV - Leslie Richards, 1979-1980 (Reel 48, Frame 1047)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV - JoAnn Robinson, 1977-1979 (Reel 48, Frame 1064)
    - Cornell University - Fellowships - Part IV - Jon Tudge, 1984 (Reel 48, Frame 1079)
    - Cornell University - Mentors for Youth, 1989-1990 (Reel 48, Frame 1089)
    - George Peabody College, 1977-1981 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
    - Hunter College of the City University of New York, 1973-1977 (Reel 49, Frame 97)
    - Hunter College of the City University of New York, 1978-1979 (Reel 49, Frame 329)
    - Program Correspondence, January-June 1973 (Reel 49, Frame 512)
    - Program Correspondence, July-December 1973 (Reel 49, Frame 665)
    - Program Correspondence, 1974 (Reel 49, Frame 950)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1974-1976 (Reel 50, Frame 1)
    - University of California, Irvine, 1975-1977 (Reel 50, Frame 317)
    - University of Minnesota, 1975-1977 (Reel 50, Frame 595)
    - University of Texas, Austin, 1975-1980 (Reel 50, Frame 695)
    - University of Virginia, 1975-1979 (Reel 50, Frame 921)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1974-1977 (Reel 51, Frame 1)
    - Yale University, 1974 (Reel 51, Frame 199)
    - Yale University, 1975 (Reel 51, Frame 432)
    - Yale University, 1976-1978 (Reel 51, Frame 599)
  - General Grants, 1976-1995; 4
    Public and private groups, and academic, religious, and other non-profit organizations supporting an improved quality of life for children through social science research, legal advocacy, and support services, are represented in this subseries. Although a number of 'local' New York City groups received support from the FCD, support was also extended to organizations throughout the United States.
    Throughout this period, the Foundation sought to integrate the efforts of child-development scholars and those who affected public policy. Grants reflecting this interest include the Foundation's support for the Family Impact Seminar at George Washington University and for Vanderbilt University's Center for the Study of Families and Children.
    Another recipient of Foundation support on behalf of children's advocacy was the Lower East Side Family Union in New York City, which provided community-based services to underprivileged children and families.
    Grants for the Congressional Science Fellowships in Child Development are documented on reels 88, 89, and 90.
    - Series 4.4 - Grant Programs - General Grants, 1976-1995 (Reel 51, Frame 743)
    - Academy for Local and State Government, 1990-1992 (Reel 51, Frame 744)
    - Action for Children's Television, 1982-1983 (Reel 51, Frame 812)
    - Advocacy Small Grants Programs, 1982-1984, 1990 (Reel 51, Frame 901)
    - Advocates for Children of New York, Inc., 1986, 1988-1993 (Reel 51, Frame 966)
    - Agenda for Children Tomorrow, 1989-1990 (Reel 51, Frame 1074)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1980-1988 (Reel 52, Frame 1)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1989-1990 (Reel 52, Frame 116)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics, 1989-1991 (Reel 52, Frame 249)
    - American Bar Association Fund for Public Education, 1981-1983 (Reel 52, Frame 299)
    - American Bar Association Fund for Public Education, 1984-1985 (Reel 52, Frame 471)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1989-1991 (Reel 52, Frame 733)
    - American Enterprise Institute - Seminar Report, 1990 (Reel 53, Frame 1)
    - American Psychological Association - Division 7, 1976-1979 (Reel 53, Frame 393)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1988-1989 (Reel 53, Frame 549)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1990 (Reel 53, Frame 753)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1991 (Reel 54, Frame 1)
    - American Reading Council, 1986-1989 (Reel 54, Frame 368)
    - Arizona Advocates for Children, 1988-1989 (Reel 54, Frame 422)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, 1987-1990 (Reel 54, Frame 428)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1981 (Reel 54, Frame 660)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1982-1983 (Reel 54, Frame 957)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies - Wye Plantation Conference, 1979-1980, 1982 (Reel 55, Frame 1)
    - Association of Junior Leagues, Inc., 1986-1987 (Reel 55, Frame 239)
    - Bank Street College of Education, 1988-1991 (Reel 55, Frame 248)
    - Barnard College, 1987-1991 (Reel 55, Frame 429)
    - Bazelton Center for Mental Health Law, 1989-1994 (Reel 55, Frame 569)
    - Bertram M. Beck - Belding Scholar, 1987 (Reel 55, Frame 659)
    - Bureau of Social Science Research, 1982-1983 (Reel 55, Frame 669)
    - Center for Family Life in Sunset Park, 1980-1983 (Reel 55, Frame 1041)
    - Center for Family Life in Sunset Park, 1984-1986 (Reel 56, Frame 3)
    - Center for Family Life in Sunset Park, 1987-1988 (Reel 56, Frame 200)
    - Center for Family Life in Sunset Park, 1989-1990 (Reel 56, Frame 492)
    - Center for Family Life in Sunset Park, 1991 (Reel 56, Frame 727)
    - Center for Family Life in Sunset Park, 1992 (Reel 56, Frame 961)
    - Center for Family Life in Sunset Park, 1993 (Reel 57, Frame 1)
    - Center for Human Resource Research, 1986 (Reel 57, Frame 185)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1988-1989 (Reel 57, Frame 217)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1990-1991 (Reel 57, Frame 603)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1992-1993 (Reel 57, Frame 990)
    - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities, 1988-1991 (Reel 58, Frame 2)
    - Center on Media and Values, 1990-1991 (Reel 58, Frame 267)
    - Child and Family Policy Center, 1989-1992 (Reel 58, Frame 315)
    - Child Care, Inc., 1983-1989 (Reel 58, Frame 597)
    - Child Care Action Campaign, 1984-1985, 1987-1988 (Reel 58, Frame 793)
    - Child Care Employee Project, 1985-1986, 1990-1992 (Reel 58, Frame 895)
    - Child Care Law Center, 1985 (Reel 59, Frame 1)
    - Child Care Staff Education Project, 1987 (Reel 59, Frame 115)
    - Child Welfare League of America, 1989-1991 (Reel 59, Frame 258)
    - Children Now, 1991-1992 (Reel 59, Frame 355)
    - Children of Alcoholics Foundation, 1989-1990 (Reel 59, Frame 461)
    - Children's Aid Society, 1983, 1985, 1987-1988, 1990-1991 (Reel 59, Frame 483)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1972-1984 (Reel 59, Frame 587)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1985-1986 (Reel 59, Frame 812)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1987-1988 (Reel 59, Frame 1065)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1989 (Reel 60, Frame 1)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1990 (Reel 60, Frame 309)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1991 (Reel 60, Frame 420)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1992-1995 (Reel 60, Frame 628)
    - Children's Express Foundation, Inc., 1988-1990, 1992 (Reel 60, Frame 707)
    - Children's Foundation, 1983-1984, 1986-1988 (Reel 60, Frame 805)
    - Children's Research and Education Institute, 1984-1985 (Reel 60, Frame 943)
    - Children's Resource and Information Service, 1982 (Reel 61, Frame 1)
    - Children's Rights Project of the American Civil Liberties Union, 1983, 1985, 1987, 1989-1990 (Reel 61, Frame 9)
    - Church of the Living Hope, 1986-1990 (Reel 61, Frame 255)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc., 1979-1980 (Reel 61, Frame 303)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc., 1981 (Reel 61, Frame 488)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc., 1982-1984 (Reel 61, Frame 673)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc., 1985-1986 (Reel 61, Frame 883)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc., 1987-1990 (Reel 61, Frame 1050)
    - Citizens for Missouri's Children, 1990-1992 (Reel 62, Frame 1)
    - City Project, 1989-1990 (Reel 62, Frame 83)
    - Coalition for Children, 1986, 1988-1990 (Reel 62, Frame 96)
    - Colorado Children's Campaign, 1988 (Reel 62, Frame 251)
    - Columbia University, 1991-1993 (Reel 62, Frame 256)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work, 1981-1986 (Reel 62, Frame 510)
    - Columbia University School of Social Work, 1987-1990 (Reel 62, Frame 693)
    - Commonweal, 1987, 1989-1992 (Reel 62, Frame 925)
    - Communications Consortium Media Center, 1991-1993 (Reel 63, Frame 1)
    - Community Food Resource Center, 1989-1992 (Reel 63, Frame 100)
    - Community School District 2, Board of Education, City of New York, 1981-1983 (Reel 63, Frame 375)
    - Community School District 2, Board of Education, City of New York, 1988-1991 (Reel 63, Frame 440)
    - Community School District 17, Board of Education, City of New York, 1981, 1985 (Reel 63, Frame 622)
    - Conference of Mayors Research and Education Foundation, 1987-1989 (Reel 63, Frame 677)
    - Congressional Black Caucus Foundation, Inc., 1984-1985 (Reel 63, Frame 728)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers, 1988-1989 (Reel 63, Frame 766)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers, 1990 (Reel 64, Frame 1)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers, 1991-1992 (Reel 64, Frame 278)
    - Council on Foundations, Inc., 1976-1989 (Reel 64, Frame 492)
    - Council of State Policy and Planning Agencies, 1990-1991 (Reel 64, Frame 659)
    - Court Appointed Special Advocates, Family Court of the State of New York, 1983-1986 (Reel 64, Frame 722)
    - Court Appointed Special Advocates, Family Court of the State of New York, 1987-1989 (Reel 64, Frame 872)
    - Court Appointed Special Advocates, Family Court of the State of New York, 1990-1991 (Reel 64, Frame 994)
    - Department of Juvenile Justice Fund, Inc., 1984-1987, 1989-1991 (Reel 65, Frame 1)
    - East Harlem Block Nursery, Inc., 1984-1986 (Reel 65, Frame 252)
    - East Harlem Block Nursery, Inc., 1987-1989 (Reel 65, Frame 449)
    - East Harlem Block Nursery, Inc., 1990-1992 (Reel 65, Frame 647)
    - East Harlem Interfaith, Inc., 1984-1988 (Reel 65, Frame 907)
    - East Harlem Interfaith, Inc., 1989 (Reel 66, Frame 1)
    - East Harlem Interfaith, Inc., 1990 (Reel 66, Frame 259)
    - Education for Parenting, 1991-1992 (Reel 66, Frame 303)
    - Educational Broadcasting Corporation, 1989-1992 (Reel 66, Frame 382)
    - Emory University, 1981 (Reel 66, Frame 590)
    - Emory University, 1982 (Reel 66, Frame 933)
    - Family Resource Coalition, 1991 (Reel 66, Frame 1012)
    - Family Resource Coalition, 1992 (Reel 67, Frame 1)
    - Family Resource Coalition, 1993 (Reel 67, Frame 168)
    - Family Resource Coalition - An Evaluation of the Family Resource Coalition's Training and Support Project for State Implementing PL 10-485, 1993 (Reel 67, Frame 314)
    - Family Resource Coalition - Planting the Seeds of Change: Lessons Learned from the Family Resource Coalition's "Training and Support Project for States Implementing PL 100 - 485: The Family Support Act of 1988", 1993 (Reel 67, Frame 470)
    - Family Support Act: Conference on Research Strategies, 1989 (Reel 67, Frame 736)
    - Family Support Act Forum, 1989-1990 (Reel 67, Frame 782)
    - Family Support Act Research Advisory Activities, 1990 (Reel 67, Frame 800)
    - Far West Laboratory for Educational Research and Development, 1990-1992 (Reel 67, Frame 813)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1979, 1983-1984, 1988-1989 (Reel 67, Frame 1044)
    - Focus Project, Inc., 1991, 1993 (Reel 67, Frame 1102)
    - Food and Hunger Hotline, 1986-1987 (Reel 68, Frame 1)
    - Food Research and Action Center, 1981-1983, 1985 (Reel 68, Frame 77)
    - Fordham University, 1988-1992 (Reel 68, Frame 227)
    - Foundation Center, 1989-1992 (Reel 68, Frame 490)
    - Free University of Berlin, 1982 (Reel 68, Frame 726)
    - French-American Foundation, 1976-1977 (Reel 68, Frame 729)
    - French-American Foundation, 1978, 1980-1982, 1990 (Reel 68, Frame 959)
    - French-American Foundation, 1991-1992 (Reel 69, Frame 1)
    - Fund for the City of New York, 1977, 1979 (Reel 69, Frame 204)
    - Fund for the City of New York, 1980-1981, 1983 (Reel 69, Frame 368)
    - Fund for the City of New York, 1986, 1990 (Reel 69, Frame 594)
    - Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, Inc., 1986-1987 (Reel 69, Frame 809)
    - George Washington University Center for Social Policy Studies, 1990-1992 (Reel 69, Frame 847)
    - Grand Street Settlement, 1988-1992 (Reel 69, Frame 948)
    - Grantmakers in Health, 1991-1993 (Reel 69, Frame 1124)
    - Harvard University - Center for Health and Human Resources Policy, John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1989 (Reel 70, Frame 1)
    - Harvard University - Center for Health and Human Resources Policy, John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1990-1991 (Reel 70, Frame 177)
    - Harvard University - Center for Health and Human Resources Policy, John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1992 (Reel 70, Frame 433)
    - Harvard University - Department of Psychology and Social Relations, 1976, 1981, 1983 (Reel 70, Frame 499)
    - Harvard University School of Public Health, 1990-1992 (Reel 70, Frame 781)
    - Henry Street Settlement, 1985-1987 (Reel 70, Frame 822)
    - Henry Street Settlement, 1988-1989 (Reel 70, Frame 896)
    - Human Development Center of Mississippi, 1990-1992 (Reel 70, Frame 1004)
    - Institute for Alternative Futures, 1979-1980 (Reel 71, Frame 1)
    - Institute for American Values, 1988-1990 (Reel 71, Frame 87)
    - Institute for Basic Research in Developmental Disabilities, 1992 (Reel 71, Frame 163)
    - Institute for Educational Leadership, Inc., 1989-1990 (Reel 71, Frame 221)
    - Institute of Judicial Administration, 1986-1988 (Reel 71, Frame 234)
    - International Social Service American Branch, Inc., 1985-1986 (Reel 71, Frame 334)
    - International Society for the Study of Behavioral Development, 1983-1984, 1986-1989 (Reel 71, Frame 438)
    - JOBS Program, 1990-1991 (Reel 71, Frame 467)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1985, 1987 (Reel 71, Frame 521)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Institute for Policy Studies, 1989-1991 (Reel 71, Frame 736)
    - Joint Action for Children - New York Interface Development Project, 1980-1982 (Reel 71, Frame 764)
    - Juvenile Law Center, 1988-1990 (Reel 71, Frame 951)
    - Kentucky Youth Advocates, Inc., 1984-1986 (Reel 71, Frame 1054)
    - Kentucky Youth Advocates, Inc., 1988-1989 (Reel 72, Frame 1)
    - Kentucky Youth Advocates, Inc., 1990-1993 (Reel 72, Frame 146)
    - Leake & Watts Children's Home, Inc., 1988-1990 (Reel 72, Frame 334)
    - Legal Advocacy on Behalf of Children, 1979 (Reel 72, Frame 365)
    - Legal Advocacy on Behalf of Children, 1980 (Reel 72, Frame 534)
    - Legal Advocacy on Behalf of Children, 1981-1986 (Reel 72, Frame 744)
    - Legal Advocacy Workshop, 1979, 1981 (Reel 72, Frame 1005)
    - Legal Advocacy Workshop, 1982 (Reel 73, Frame 1)
    - Legal Advocacy Workshop, 1983 (Reel 73, Frame 372)
    - Legal Advocacy Workshop, 1984 (Reel 73, Frame 483)
    - Legal Advocacy Workshop, 1985-1986 (Reel 73, Frame 726)
    - Little Sisters of the Assumption, 1986-1987, 1989-1990 (Reel 73, Frame 767)
    - Lower East Side Family Union, Inc., 1977-1978, 1980, 1982-1984, 1987, 1989 (Reel 73, Frame 824)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation, 1988-1991 (Reel 74, Frame 1)
    - Maryland Advocates for Children and Youth, Inc., 1991-1992, 1995 (Reel 74, Frame 252)
    - Massachusetts Advocacy Center, 1988-1989 (Reel 74, Frame 282)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1979-1982, 1984 (Reel 74, Frame 293)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1985-1989 (Reel 74, Frame 449)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1990-1992 (Reel 74, Frame 644)
    - Metropolitan Assistance, 1989-1993 (Reel 74, Frame 841)
    - Michigan Evaluation Research Center, 1980-1983 (Reel 74, Frame 1028)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy, 1975-1976 (Reel 75, Frame 1)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy, 1977 (Reel 75, Frame 99)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy, 1978 (Reel 75, Frame 334)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy - Part I, 1979 (Reel 75, Frame 705)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy - Part II, 1979 (Reel 75, Frame 985)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy, 1980 (Reel 76, Frame 1)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy, 1981 (Reel 76, Frame 204)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy, 1982-1984 (Reel 76, Frame 484)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - Committee on Child Development Research and Public Policy, 1987-1997 (Reel 76, Frame 637)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - National Forum on the Future of Children and Families, 1991-1992 (Reel 76, Frame 736)
    - National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council - National Observatory of Child Development, 1977-1978 (Reel 76, Frame 794)
    - National Association for the Education of Young Children, 1982-1985 (Reel 77, Frame 1)
    - National Black Child Development Institute, 1982, 1984-1985 (Reel 77, Frame 66)
    - National Black Child Development Institute, 1987 (Reel 77, Frame 228)
    - National Black Child Development Institute, 1988-1989 (Reel 77, Frame 487)
    - National Black Child Development Institute, 1990 (Reel 77, Frame 663)
    - National Black Child Development Institute, 1991 (Reel 77, Frame 789)
    - National Center for Children in Poverty, 1992 (Reel 77, Frame 927)
    - National Center for Children in Poverty - Supplementary Information, 1991-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1)
    - National Center for Clinical Infant Programs, 1986-1989 (Reel 78, Frame 527)
    - National Center for Policy Alternatives, 1990-1991 (Reel 78, Frame 659)
    - National Commission on Children, 1989-1990 (Reel 78, Frame 773)
    - National Commission on Children, 1991 (Reel 78, Frame 896)
    - National Committee for Adoption, 1988-1991 (Reel 79, Frame 1)
    - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1988-1989 (Reel 79, Frame 65)
    - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1990-1991 (Reel 79, Frame 219)
    - National Council of Churches, 1982-1983 (Reel 79, Frame 460)
    - National Governors' Association - Center for Policy Research, 1982-1988 (Reel 79, Frame 520)
    - National Governors' Association - Center for Policy Research, 1989 (Reel 79, Frame 714)
    - National Governors' Association - Center for Policy Research, 1990 (Reel 79, Frame 1032)
    - National Governors' Association - Center for Policy Research, 1991-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 1)
    - National Institute on Children, Youth and Families, 1991 (Reel 80, Frame 162)
    - National League of Cities, 1986-1988 (Reel 80, Frame 181)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1983-1984 (Reel 80, Frame 500)
    - New Alternatives for Children, Inc., 1984-1988 (Reel 80, Frame 531)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, 1988-1989 (Reel 80, Frame 552)